adx-pro.com 2019-03-21

# ADX Holdings | Privacy Policy

**Privacy and Data Protection Information**

Pursuant to the GDPR and the German privacy and data protection legislation, Adx Holdings Limited (www.adx-pro.com/privacy) hereby explains its current Privacy and Data Protection Policies.

If you would like to get any further information about these policies, or if you think we may have personal information about you that is relevant in terms of data protection, please contact our external data protection officer at privacy@adx-pro.com.

 **General Information**

ADX PRO treats the protection of your personal data with high priority and vows to fully comply with the applicable legislation and directives as set forth by the European Union and the Federal Republic of Germany. 

This Privacy and Data Protection Information explains why and how accessing our website www.adx-pro.com becomes relevant in terms of personal data processing, storage and use, and we also indicate how this applies to other websites linking to our website. 

This document further indicates what we do to protect your personal data when you are using our website.

 **Personal Data**

Personal Data allow for identification of natural persons. Name, address, email, and similar information qualify as personal data. 

Accessing and using our website is possible without sharing fully or in part your personal information with us or any other third party.

If you decide to use our contact fields or use the email links to submit information on our website, we will receive personal information, which is the information that you share in our contact fields or by sending us an email. 

Your decision to submit this information is understood as an intrinsic part of contacting us, for we wouldn’t be able to get back to you without your personal information. 

If you contact us through this website, you will be in control of the information that you submit and decide to share.

 **Data Processing as part of using our website**

As any other website, ADX PRO has a website that is hosted on a webserver, and in order to be able to provide the site to users, this server collects information, processes the same and logs it. 

This information is provided by your webbrowser, and it will be:

-The browser type that you are using including the version

-The operating system on which your browser is running

-The referrer URL, which indicates the website that you came from to access ours

-The user IP, i.e. the hostname of the user

-The time and date of the server call

-The type of request

The data is stored by our host and we can access the information, e.g. to understand technical problems. 

However, we do not combine this information or process it in combination with any other data. 

The information will be erased completely after 31 days. 

The logfiles on our server primarily serve the purpose to identify causes of technical problems and, even more, to prevent and protect against criminal activity as well as to help official authorities identify perpetrators.

 **Processing personal data from this website**

If you choose to contact us, we will process your personal data only to answer your request. 

We will receive your submitted information by email and may forward this information internally to the staff member in charge of the topic you are contacting us about. 

We inform you that we store information according to the legal requirements, e.g. if taxation or penal law puts this obligation on us.

 **Forwarding of personal information to third parties**

We will not forward your personal information to third parties unless this is relevant to answering your request or if legally permitted or required. 

If we forward personal data to third parties, this will be handled according to the legal requirements for this process. 

The data that we share will only be the minimal data needed to achieve the target for which we are contacting the third party.

 **Your right to information and to delete personal data**

If you would like to understand which of your personal data we may have stored or if you would like to understand how this data is being processed in our company, please contact us. 

We will share this information free of charge and in the timeliest possible manner. 

You can also receive an electronic report from us. 

If you ask us to review, change or delete personal data belonging to you, we will immediately do so unless legal requirements prohibit the same.

 **Cookies**

In order to analyze the use patterns, get comprehensive statistics, identify problems and reach optimizations for our website, we are using so-called ‘cookies’. 

Cookies are small text files that will be stored on the visitor’s device, saved in the client of the user. 

Most cookies used on this website are session-related and will be removed automatically when you leave the site. 

Please note that we don’t use cookies to store personal information. 

In the context of this website, cookies are mostly used to receive website statistics from Google Analytics. 

Our cookies will not cause any harm on your device and will have no effect on your system’s performance. 

If you choose to delete or block cookies, our website will still remain functional without limitations.

 **Social Plugins and Social Media Buttons**

This website uses so called Social Plugins, services provided by Social Media Platforms. 

We are working with Social Plugins for Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn.

 **Facebook**

Please note that we have Social Plugins to allow you to share blog posts from our site on Facebook. 

To the best of our knowledge and to protect your data we undertake the maximum and promise that we will not automatically share data with Facebook as a part of your visit to our site. 

However, it is possible and beyond our control that Facebook may collect personal data whenever you decide to interact with the Social Media Icon displayed on our site. 

That said, we would like to inform you about the general process of Social Plugins by Facebook.

Facebook is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). 

Facebook plugins are marked with a Facebook logo or the addition “Social Plug-in of Facebook” or “Facebook Social Plug-in”. 

An overview of the Facebook plugins and their appearance can be found [here](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/).

If you interact with the plugins, for example, press the “F” button in our blog or leave a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted directly to a Facebook server and stored there. 

The information will also be published on Facebook and displayed to your Facebook friends or third parties. 

Facebook may use this information for the purpose of advertising, market research and tailor-made Facebook pages. 

For this purpose, Facebook uses usage, interest and relationship profiles, e.g. to evaluate the use of our website in relation to the advertisements displayed on Facebook, to inform other Facebook users about your activities on our website and to provide other services related to the use of Facebook. 

If you do not want Facebook to associate the data collected through our website with your Facebook account, you must log out of Facebook before visiting our website. 

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your related rights and settings options for the protection of your privacy, please [refer to the privacy policy of Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update).

 **Twitter**

This website uses the buttons of the Twitter service. 

These buttons are provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA (“Twitter”). 

They are recognizable by terms like “Twitter” combined with a stylized bird. 

With the help of the buttons it is possible to share a post or a page within our website on Twitter or to follow us on Twitter.

Please note that your data will only be shared with Twitter if you decide to do so by clicking on the icon. 

It is possible and beyond our control that Twitter may collect personal data whenever you decide to interact with the Social Media Icon displayed on our site.

To prevent Twitter from collecting the above information on our website, log out of Twitter before visiting our website. 

To prevent general access from Twitter to your data on our and other websites, you can exclude Twitter social plugins with an add-on for your browser (e.g., Twitter Blocker). 

For more information, [see the privacy policy of Twitter](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).

 **LinkedIn**

On our website there are social network plugins from LinkedIn, LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“LinkedIn”). 

The LinkedIn plugins can be recognized by the LinkedIn logo or the “recommendation button” on our website.

It is possible and beyond our control that LinkedIn may collect personal data whenever you decide to interact with the Social Media Icon displayed on our site. 

Please note that your data will only be shared with LinkedIn if you decide to do so by clicking on the icon.

If you click the LinkedIn button while logged in to your LinkedIn account, you can link the contents of our website to your LinkedIn profile. 

This allows LinkedIn to associate your visit to our website with your user account. 

We point out that we are not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by LinkedIn. 

To prevent LinkedIn from collecting the above information on our website, log out of LinkedIn before visiting our website. 

For information on the purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by LinkedIn, as well as your rights and options for protecting your privacy, please [refer to LinkedIn’s privacy policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).

 **Pinterest**

Our website integrates plugins from Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA, 94301, USA (“Pinterest”). 

These plugins can be recognized by the “pin it button” or the word “Pinterest” in a button on our website.

If you click on such a button while logged in to your Pinterest account, you can link the contents of our website to your Pinterest profile. 

This allows Pinterest to associate your visit to our website with your user account. 

We point out that we are not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Pinterest. 

To prevent Pinterest from collecting the above information on our website, log out of Pinterest before visiting our website.

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Pinterest as well as your rights in this regard and setting options for the protection of your privacy, [please refer to the privacy policy of Pinterest](https://policy.pinterest.com/en-gb/privacy-policy).

 **Google +1**

Our site uses the “+1” social network button Google+ operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). 

The button is recognizable by the sign “+1” or another lettering pointing to Google.

Here too, we have set up our website in such a way that your data and any information will only be shared if you explicitly decide to.

We do not control the amount of data Google collects from the button, but we do assume your IP address is being tracked. 

If you are a Google+ member and do not want Google to collect information about you from our website and associate it with your member data stored on Google, you must log out of Google+ before visiting our website. 

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Google, as well as your rights in this regard and setting options for the protection of your privacy can be found in the [privacy policy of Google](https://developers.google.com/+/web/buttons-policy).

 **AdNovation**

To become a partner and cooperate with us, you need to set up an account with our technical partner and data processor Adnovation B.V, When you decide to open such an account, we will ask you to provide necessary personal and company information that will be stored in the tracking system operated by AdNovation. 

We advise you to review the [applicable policy on the AdNovation site](https://www.adifier.io/privacy).

You will also be asked to agree to the specific Data Protection and Privacy Policy upon signing up for a ADX PRO account at this site: http://dashboard.adx-pro.com/

 **Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to analyze the performance and use patterns of our website and its content. 

For this paragraph, we use the text provided by copyright owner intersoft consulting.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc, (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; Google). 

The use includes the Universal Analytics operating mode. 

This facilitates the assignment of data, sessions and interactions across several devices to a pseudonymous user ID and thus the analysis of a user’s activities across devices. 

Google Analytics uses cookies to allow the website operator to analyze how users use the site. 

The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, if IP anonymisation is activated on this website, Google will reduce your IP address within Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area beforehand. 

Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. 

The IP address transmitted by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. 

On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide the website operator with other services related to website and Internet use. 

Our legitimate interest in data processing also lies in these purposes. 

The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is § 15 para. 3 TMG and Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

The data sent by us and linked to cookies, user-identifiers (e.g. User-IDs) or advertising-identifiers are automatically deleted after 14 months. Data whose retention period has been reached is automatically deleted once a month. 

For more information on terms of use and data protection, please visit <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html> or <https://policies.google.com/?hl=en>.

You can prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and installing the Browser Add-on. 

Opt-out cookies prevent the future collection of your data when you visit this website. 

To prevent Universal Analytics from collecting data across several devices, you must opt out on all systems used. 

If you click here, the opt-out cookie will be set: Disable Google Analytics

 **Blog Comments**

You may choose to comment blogposts, which implies your intention to have this comment and the submitted personal data published. Please note that we can decide to publicly display your comments and personal data submitted. We reserve the right to delete your comments and reject publication.

 **Changes to the Data Protection Policy**

We reserve the right to change our Data Protection Policy, especially to adapt it to new legal requirements or to keep it up-to-date with technical developments and new situations. 

Please note that this Data Protection Policy is the most current one. 

Please use it to get the valid and current information about the applicable policy for your visit on this website.
